My name's Gary Eckert,
and I've done business here at Phil's, and they're a real nice
bunch of people, and they take care of you.
I noticed that you brought donuts and coffee in. Why is that?
The reason is these people are very nice. They treat you like you're family here.
So you just decided to bring this in?
I decided to bring this in as a little thank-you note.
All right. That's pretty awesome.
So how did you come to experience Phil's?
Well, I had an old grandma run into my old truck, and on the day it happened,
I pulled into Phil's here, and they said, "We'll get you fixed up."
It took a little bit of time because my truck's old.
It's an old 1993 F-250,
so I had to get some parts, and that took a little bit of time.
All in all, the experience was great.
It's a good bunch of people here, a bunch of people that care about making sure
you're satisfied with the quality of work that they've done.